The pack is back.
Teen Wolf: The Movie is a action, fantasy, tv movie
film directed by Russell Mulcahy.
The wolves are howling once again, as a terrifying
ancient evil emerges in Beacon Hills.
Scott McCall, no longer a teenager yet still an Alpha, must gather new allies and
reunite trusted friends to fight back against this powerful and deadly enemy.
Scott McCall, played by Tyler Posey.
Allison Argent, played by Crystal Reed.
Lydia Martin, played by Holland Roden.
Derek Hale, played by Tyler Hoechlin.
Malia Tate, played by Shelley Hennig.
Chris Argent, played by JR Bourne.
Teen Wolf: The Movie is a 2023 American supernatural thriller film,
directed by Russell Mulcahy and written by Jeff Davis.
The film is the fifth installment in the franchise, and is a
continuation of the MTV series Teen Wolf.
The movie includes most of the cast reprising their roles, including Tyler Posey, Crystal Reed, Tyler Hoechlin, Holland
Roden, Colton Haynes, Shelley Hennig, Dylan Sprayberry, Linden Ashby, Melissa Ponzio, and JR Bourne.
It follows werewolf Scott McCall (Posey) as he protects
his California town from an old threat.
Teen Wolf: The Movie was released on Paramount+ on January
26, 2023, to mixed reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of sequel, werewolf,
supernatural creature, based on movie, banshee.